https://jrliggett.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy PolicyDEFINITIONS AND LEGAL REFERENCESPERSONAL DATA (OR DATA)Any information that directly, indirectly, or in connection with other information — including a personal identification number — allows for the identification or identifiability of a natural person.USAGE DATAInformation collected automatically through this website (or third-party services employed in this website), which can include: the IP addresses or domain names of the computers utilized by the users who use this website, the URI addresses (Uniform Resource Identifier), the time of the request, the method utilized to submit the request to the server, the size of the file received in response, the numerical code indicating the status of the server’s answer (successful outcome, error, etc.), the country of origin, the features of the browser and the operating system utilized by the user, the various time details per visit (e.g., the time spent on each page within the website) and the details about the path followed within the website with special reference to the sequence of pages visited, and other parameters about the device operating system and/or the User’s IT environment.USERThe individual using this website who, unless otherwise specified, coincides with the data subject.DATA SUBJECTThe natural person to whom the personal data refers.DATA PROCESSORThe natural or legal person, public authority, agency or other body which processes personal data on behalf of the controller, as described in this privacy policy.DATA CONTROLLERThe natural or legal person, public authority, agency or other body which, alone or jointly with others, determines the purposes and means of the processing of personal data, including the security measures concerning the operation and use of this website. The data controller, unless otherwise specified, is the owner of this website.THIS WEBSITEThe means by which the personal data of the user is collected and processed.TYPES OF DATA COLLECTEDAmong the types of personal data that this website collects, by itself or through third parties, there are: cookies, username, email address, various types of data, usage data, website, first name and last name. Complete details on each type of personal data collected are provided in the dedicated sections of this privacy policy or by specific explanation texts displayed prior to the data collection. Personal data may be freely provided by the user, or, in case of usage data, collected automatically when using this website. Unless specified otherwise, all data requested by this website is mandatory and failure to provide this data may make it impossible for this website to provide its services. In cases where this website specifically states that some data is not mandatory, users are free not to communicate this data without consequences to the availability or the functioning of the service. Users who are uncertain about which personal data is mandatory are welcome to contact CodexThemes. Any use of cookies – or of other tracking tools – by this website or by the owners of third-party services used by this website serves the purpose of providing the service required by the user, in addition to any other purposes described in the present document and in the cookie policy. Users are responsible for any third-party personal data obtained, published or shared through this website and confirm that they have the third party’s consent to provide the data to the owner.MODE AND PLACE OF PROCESSING THE DATAMETHODS OF PROCESSINGCodexThemes takes appropriate security measures to prevent unauthorized access, disclosure, modification, or unauthorized destruction of the data. The data processing is carried out using computers and/or IT enabled tools, following organizational procedures and modes strictly related to the purposes indicated. In addition to CodexThemes, in some cases, the data may be accessible to certain types of external parties (such as third-party technical service providers, mail carriers, hosting providers, IT companies, communications agencies) appointed, if necessary, as data processors. The updated list of these parties may be requested from CodexThemes at any time.LEGAL BASIS OF PROCESSINGCodexThemes may process personal data relating to users if one of the following applies:provision of data is necessary for the performance of an agreement with the user and/or for any pre-contractual obligations thereofprocessing is necessary for compliance with a legal obligation to which CodexThemes is subjectprocessing is related to a task that is carried out in the public interest or in the exercise of official authority vested in CodexThemesprocessing is necessary for the purposes of the legitimate interests pursued by CodexThemes or by a third party.In any case, CodexTheme will gladly help to clarify the specific legal basis that applies to the processing, and in particular whether the provision of personal data is a statutory or contractual requirement, or a requirement necessary to enter into a contract.
